13具尸体 全部为女性...
Thirteen bodies, all female...
11个白人 2个疑似亚洲人
eleven White, two Asian-looking.
年龄都在20到30之间 已经彻底僵硬
All between the ages of maybe 20, 30. All very dead.
很可能是从东欧来的
From Eastern Europe probably.
那么 这是一起意外咯?
So this is, what, an accident?
顶上的通风管被压瘪了 很可能发生在卸货时
Your air pipe's up top, crushed. Probably during the off-load.
那么 嗯 很可能是意外
So, yeah, accidental probably.
但他说了算 不是吗?
But that's his call, right?
医生
Doctor.
Frazier
Frazier.
嘿 我们这怎么样?
How're we doing here?
我们怎么样?
How are we doing?
我是说 我们需要做什么?
I mean, what are we doing?
这里有什么安排?
What's the plan with all this?
这是你第一次调查死亡事件吗 警官?
Is this your first death investigation, Officer?
叫我Russell
Russell.
是的 第一次也是唯一的一次
Yeah, first and onliest.
那你第一次就中了头彩 13具
You got 13 for the price of one.
我们将在下午验尸
We're gonna start cutting this afternoon.
任何你收集到的 可作身份证明的东西
Anything you got by way of identifications
都送到我办公室
should come through my office.
什么身份证明?
What identification?
目前为止 我们都还没有在这堆里 找到护照或是签证
So far, we don't have a passport or visa in the bunch.
不管你在行李箱里发现了什么 都送过来...
Whatever you find in this luggage, send it over...
否则她们只能被当成无名氏送到太平间了
or they're all going to the Anatomy Board as Jane Does.
这案子谁查?
Who's the investigating agency?
如果她们还活着 她们就是非法入境 由移民局管辖
If they were alive, they'd be illegals, and that would mean lmmigration.
但是她们死了 所以她们成了货物
But they're dead, so they're cargo.
货物 但不算走私品
Cargo, but no contraband.
不算违法海关条例
There's nothing to be seized as a customs violation.
她们是死在港务局的地盘上 对吧?
They're dead on Port Authority property, right?
- 是的 - 那就归州政府管
-Yeah. -That's a state thing.
我们会负责的
We'll eat it.
如果这只是意外 那只要找出 这些偷渡者的身份就好了 对吧
If it's accidental, then it's just about IDs on these stowaways, right?
我觉得够了 哥们
Good enough for me, brother.
我觉得没理由立案
No reason to open a full case folder that I can see.
等一等 你们刑侦科就这么走了?
Wait a minute. You CID guys are rolling out on this?
没有犯罪就不用调查
No crime, no investigation.
Russell警官 你现在的活儿就是写一堆报告
All you've got right here, Officer Russell, is a lot of paperwork.
还是孤军奋战
And then there was one.
火线重案组 第二季 第二集 城门池鱼
The Wire S02E02 Collateral Damage
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"他们可以吃了你 但总得吐出来"  ---McNulty
- 你没必要这么做 - 是吗?
- You don't have to do this. - No?
你要说的话我都对Spiros说过了
Anything you're gonna say I already said to Spiros.
你有骂他希腊猪吗?
You called him a Greek asshole?
你以为我们想这样?
You think we wanted this?
我才不知道你们这些家伙想折腾什么
I don't know what the fuck you people want and don't want.
我只知道 我的码头上有个集装箱 里面藏的所有姑娘都闷死了
All I know is, I got a can full of young girls suffocating to death on my docks.
- 这是一次失误 - 失误?
- This was a mistake. - A mistake?
她们它妈的都死在那箱子里了
They fucking died in that can...
而这狗娘养的蠢货 还坐在那优哉游哉
while this stupid son of a bitch sat there with his dick in his hands.
你什么都不知道
You know nothing.
我们知道你很生气 Frank 我们也很恼火 好吗?
We understand you're upset, Frank. We are upset, too, okay?
Sergei本该等我们的朋友下船
Sergei was supposed to wait for our friend to come off the boat.
来给我们报个平安
Our friend was supposed to tell us that there was no problem...
你瞧 没有海关
you know, no Customs.
- 可他没有下船 - 那它妈的干嘛没有?
- He did not come off the boat. - Why the fuck not?
这是我们努力想查清的  我们也不知道
This is what we're trying to find out. We don't know.
就因为你们没有收到平安信 就让这些女孩死在了我的码头上?
Because you don't get the right message, these girls are dying on my docks?
是这么回事吗? 死在我的码头上!
This is how it goes? On my docks, this happened!
我明白你的感受...
I understand how you feel...
但我们也很恼火 所有人 大家都很恼火
but we're upset, too. Everybody, we're all upset.
没人希望发生这事
Nobody here wanted this.
Frank叔叔 他们说了 不是故意的
Uncle Frank, they're saying it wasn't on purpose.
你本可以告诉我 它妈的集装箱里藏了姑娘
You could've told me there were girls in that fucking can.
要是你告诉了我 我就不会再把她们
You could've told me, so I didn't just shove them back...
塞回那里 知道吗?
in the stacks like I did, right?
你们干嘛不告诉我 那个该死的集装箱里有什么?
Why didn't you tell me what was in that motherfucking can?
现在你想知道集装箱里有什么了?
Now you want to know what's in the cans?
之前 你还什么都不想知道 现在 你想问了
Before, you wanted to know nothing. Now, you ask.
有枪 知道么
Guns, okay?
毒品 妓女 伏特加 宝马车...
Drugs, whores, vodka, BMWs...
白鲟鱼子酱:每磅超过1000美金
也许还有白鲟鱼子酱和炸弹
beluga caviar or bombs, maybe.
邪恶的恐怖分子携带着巨型核弹
Bad terrorists with big nuclear bombs.
我在开玩笑 Frank 只是个笑话
I am kidding you, Frank, it's a joke.
但是你不问...
But you don't ask...
因为你不想知道
because you don't want to know.
告诉"希腊人" 要是下次有什么活物
Tell the Greek that next time he's got something breathing...
在那些集装箱里 得先通知我
in one of them cans, I need to know it.
给他几天时间 好吧
Give him a couple of days, you know?
那么Roberto被抓住了?
So Roberto been caught?
是的 药管局在纽约抓了他
Yep, DEA got him in New York.
这下有点意思了
Now the shit makes some sense.
我们送去的上一单钱退回来了
The money we sent for the last go-round came back.
全部
All of it.
该死的 他们现在要和我们撇清关系了?
Damn, they ain't gonna touch us now?
该死的多米尼加人夹着尾巴跑 怕得像是我们是祸害
Goddamn Dominicans running around scared acting like we the problem.
Roberto甚至不愿见我们
Roberto won't even see us.
Stringer得去律师那
Stringer had to go to the lawyer up there.
他们说他们得确认完后 才能再和我们合作
They saying they have to be sure before they get back with us.
他们说你才判了7年 所以...
They saying you only got seven years, so--
所以 我它妈的告了密?
So I'm a motherfucking snitch?
他们没这么说
They ain't saying they think it.
他们只是不知道 联邦调查局是怎么查到Roberto的
They just don't know how the Feds got to Roberto.
所以我们现在被排斥了
So we on the outside.
没错
Yep.
瞧...
Look...
我们现在就是靠些垃圾 在维持公房区的生意
we hanging on to them projects with scraps.
Avon 你得给我们找个人
Avon, you gotta have somebody for us.
有个在Atlanta的朋友...
A friend in Atlanta...
自己开了家车轱辘店 叫Vargus
owns a rim shop, name of Vargus.
让Stringer明天飞过去找他
Have Stringer fly down there tomorrow and meet him.
你最近有看到D'Angelo吗?
You seen D'Angelo lately?
他在J区 你懂我的意思吗?
He on the J-tier, you know what I mean?
我要过去很难 你懂吗
It's very difficult for me to get over there, you know?
那么你没去看他
So you ain't checking on him,
而Donette也野在外面
and Donette's out and about.
我现在什么都不知道了
I don't know what's what anymore.
Donette是怎么了?
Now, what's up with Donette?
我留了言 但是她不回电话
I leave messages, she ain't call back.
她也没有按时到这里来
She ain't had her ass down here regular neither.
我们不能睁只眼闭只眼了 Avon
We need to tighten shit up, Avon.
她应该每个星期都带他儿子来
She should be bringing his son by every week.
对 我也会让Stringer盯紧这事
Yeah, I'm gonna put Stringer on that, too.
在他为我们做了这一切之后...
After all he has done for us...
Dee需要得到照顾 Avon
Dee needs to be cared for, Avon.
- 你答应过的 - 我知道
- Promises were made. - I know.
他认了20年的罪 毫无怨言
He took the 20, he ain't complaining.
他为这家担了很多
He is carrying a lot of weight for this family.
我们是想笼络他
And we keeping him close.
但是Dee现在对我很冷淡
Dee being cold toward me right now.
他现在它妈的还在"调整"自己
He in this motherfucker trying to make adjustments and shit.
调整?
Adjustments?
Brianna...
你很清楚我不会让他有事的 对吧
you know damn well I ain't gonna let shit happen to him, right?
1号审讯室
你从船上弄来的?
You got these off the boat?
什么 在冬天?
What, in winter?
几个月里吧
In a couple of months.
额外福利吧
Fringe benefit.
在凶杀组可抓不到螃蟹 对吧?
Can't catch crabs in Homicide, right?
除了也许偶尔有急症室的护士
Except maybe the occasional emergency room nurse...
出没一下
every now and again.
这里得换点气了
Need some air in here.
别 别 别
Leave it.
我可不想Rawls经过的时候找骂
I don't need the hassle if Rawls comes past.
你不是一般的混蛋 对吧 Jimmy?
You're not the run-of-the-mill kind of asshole, are you?
你可是独一无二的混球啊
You're the special kind of asshole.
我是很特别 好吧
I'm special, all right.
你花了多长时间 搞清楚那些潮汐
How long did it take you to figure out the tide...
把那女孩送过了交接线?
took that girl over the county line?
三小时
Three hours.
三小时...
Three hours...
用你那小小的港口地图...
with your little harbor maps...
和你的潮汐表 就为了给Rawls多塞具尸体
and your tide tables just to stick Rawls with an extra body.
更别提你给Cole找了件大悬案
Never mind that you just fucked Cole with a stone whodunit.
- 那是殃及池鱼 - 嗯
- That's collateral damage. - Yeah.
你要浪费蟹黄?
Are you gonna waste that crab gut?
看来你更是个娘们 Jimmy
You're a pussy, besides, Jimmy.
- 我们需要Omar Jimmy - 你看这个
- We need Omar, Jimmy. - You see this.
- 十三个女孩? - 是的 我听说了
- Thirteen girls? - Yeah, I heard about it.
谁的案子?
Who caught it?
反正不是我们
It ain't ours.
港口警局有对Patapsco河的管辖权
Port police has jurisdiction over Patapsco.
反正也不是谋杀 谁会多管闲事啊
Ain't gonna be a murder either, so who gives a fuck?
听着 Jimmy 我可拿不下Bird这案子
Listen, Jimmy, I ain't got no case on Bird...
除非那混蛋疯子Omar作证 你听到我说的了吗?
unless that crazy motherfucker Omar testifies. You hear me?
是时候你给Bunk展示你的爱了
It's time you show Bunk the love.
你想要爱 就过来坐我的大腿
You want love, you come and sit on my lap.
操
Shit.
那个婊子养的过来跟我说...
This pretty motherfucker comes over and tells me...
码头上那海关的封条破了 要我负责
the customs seal got broke on the dock and I'm responsible.
它妈的你信吗?
Can you fucking believe that?
我在吊车上就看到这该死的玩意早破了
I seen the goddamn thing on the crane, the seal's already broke.
谁干的?
Who got to it?
很可能是船员 一些该死的水手
The crew probably. Some goddamn ordinary seamen.
- 什么货? - 伏特加吧 我想
- What was it? - Vodka, I think.
我没说我们没有顺个一两箱...
I ain't saying we didn't squeeze a case or two...
但是去它的 Frank 整个集装箱都已经开了
but fuck it, Frank, the can was already open.
得了吧 Tommy 你当我没见过猫腻吗
I didn't come to the union hall today on the back of no bread truck.
我发誓 Frank 我们就在最后拿了几箱...
I swear, Frank, we grabbed a couple cases at the end...
还是在那些水手风卷残云之后
after everyone of them sailor boys damn near raped it.
- 只有几箱? - 是的 四箱
- A couple of cases? - Yeah, it was four.
那些警察搞毛啊?
What the fuck is up with the police?
什么?
What?
他们它妈的给每辆车都开了单子
They're stroking tickets on every fucking car.
"后车牌无法完全可见"?
"Rear tag not entirely visible?"
你的拖曳杆装得高了
You got the tow bar set high.
"紧急通道被堵塞" 你跟我开什么玩笑?
"Emergency access blocked." Are you kidding me?
自从该死的船有了帆篷起
We've been parking this side of the building
我们就把车停在大楼这一侧了
since the fucking ships had sails.
拜托 老兄 到底怎么回事?
Come on, pal, what the fuck?
不是我 是我的头儿
It ain't me, it's my boss.
谁是你的头儿?
Who's your boss?
Valchek 东南区
Valchek, Southeast district.
Stan Valchek?
区警长 是的
The district commander, yeah.
这个矮冬瓜 他干嘛忍我们?
That sawed-off piece of shit. Why the hell is he fucking with us?
不管是什么 反正他卯上你们了...
Whatever it's about, you definitely got the man's attention...
因为今天早上我长官就放话了
'cause word comes down this morning from my shift lieutenant...
我们一天得来你们工会大院巡逻两次 给车子开罚单
we're to ride past your union hall twice a day and paper cars.
你在给个脑残卖命
You work for a gaping asshole.
其实不止一个
More than one actually.
你知道我们不会忍气吞声的 我们会上访到市里
We're not gonna put up with this shit, we're gonna go downtown on it.
闹到市长办公室去吧
Take it all the way to the mayor's office,
我不怪你 但是别把我卷进去
I can't blame you, but leave me out of it.
他是官 我是兵
It's chain of command.
我是说 我也得忍受那婊子养的 对吧?
I mean, I gotta live with the son of a bitch, too, right?
你怎么能说这地方不干净?
You can't tell me this place ain't clean.
我没让你开口就不准讲话
You talk when I say you can.
谁让你布置了 小子?
Who told you to decorate, nigger?
我看这屋子乱透了
Cell look pretty fucked up to me.
你管这叫干净?
What you calling clean?
- 伙计 我什么都没干 - 别敷衍我 混蛋!
- Man, I ain't done shit. - Don't say that to me, motherfucker!
还有宠物?
Pets, too?
不 你瞧 它们是塑料的 只有个小马达而已 哥们
No, you see, they plastic, they got little motors and all, man.
在宵禁之前把这里弄干净了
Clean this shit before lock-down.
连续四次了 娘的!
That's four in a row, bitch!
在这儿等着 不会很久
Wait here, this won't take long.
你想从我这得到什么? 他是E级的 而你才是个"G"
What do you want from me? He's an E-rate and you're a "G."
他想要这船 只能给他咯
He wants the ship, he gets the ship.
资历 Mims 资历
Seniority, Mims, seniority.
没了它 工会也就不存在了 老兄
There ain't no union without it, brother.
你的甜心来了
Your sweetheart's out there.
谁?
Who?
我得挂了 Mims 我得挂了
I gotta go, Mims, I got to.
这里有点空荡荡啊
Kind of empty in here.
大家都在干活
Everyone's working.
你收到话了?
You getting the message?
什么话?
The message?
从复活节开始我就让工人 为圣Casmir教堂的中堂打造窗户了
I had people working on a window for the nave up St. Casmir's since Easter...
你知道吗?
you know that?
我从六个不同的人那收到捐款
I took money from half a dozen different people...
告诉他们钱会花到哪儿
told them where it was gonna go.
你跟Lewandowski神父说了?
You tell Father Lewandowski?
我是打算给他个惊喜
I was gonna surprise him.
是啊 你让大家都惊喜了
Yeah, you surprised everybody.
结果"僧多粥少"了 对吗?
Now there's one window too many, right?
还有件事 Lew神父说...
Here's the thing, Father Lew says...
他可以在二楼内殿也可以按一个
he could take another window in the rectory on the second floor.
对你来说不错啊
Good for you.
不 是你走运 Frank
No, good for you, Frank.
不想让我瞎了你的狗眼 就放聪明 上道点
You don't want my finger in your eye, you better do what's right here.
什么是上道?
What's right?
上道应该是你恭恭敬敬地来我这儿
What's right would be for you to come down here to my house...
点头哈腰 有求于我
Iike a decent human being and ask a common courtesy.
但那就不是你了 不是你的做派
But that's not you, it's not your way.
我家老头子一直说 你从小
My old man always said you were a half-ass punk...
在圣Redeemer教区里就是个小混混
over at Holy Redeemer as a kid.
我姐姐说你在天主教青年会的舞会上 简直是个可恶的讨厌鬼
My sister said you were a pain in the ass pest at all them CYO dances...
没有哪个姑娘愿意看你一眼
where none of the girls would even look at you.
在你得到你警徽的时候 这里几乎所有人都在说
Damn near everyone at the Point said when you got your badge...
姓Valchek的警察遍地开花
it was too much for anybody named Valchek to have a patrolman's drag.
无容置疑 从那天起 你就成了地地道道的人渣
And sure enough, you've been an official asshole every day since.
滚你的吧 还有你的窗户!
Fuck you! And your window!
你要去哪儿?
Where are you gonna be?
也许我会找个地方吃午饭
I'm gonna go find some lunch somewhere, maybe.
准我离开一个小时 行吗?
Give me an hour, yeah?
行
Yeah.
这它妈的啥玩意儿?
What the fuck is this?
结啊
A knot.
兔子耳朵：水手结里最常用的一种八字扣
你干嘛不直接弄个"兔子耳朵"?
Why don't you just do bunny ears?
那我们还有什么收获?
So what else we got?
药品 衣物 铺盖 就这些
Medics, clothes, bedrolls, that's it.
不过还有封信
Here's a letter, though.
信? 什么语言?
A letter? What language?
谁知道
Who knows?
写得跟天书似的
Same backwards-ass writing, though.
我敢说 应该像是俄文之类的
That's like Russian or something, I'm telling you.
猜不出名字和地址...
Can't figure the name or the address...
但是邮票上有"Magyar"(匈牙利)
but the stamp says "Magyar" on it.
Magyar在哪儿?
Where's Magyar?
你当我是什么 Rand McNally(GPS导航仪)?
What the hell do I look like, Rand McNally?
你们中的哪位探员发现了这些死去的姑娘?
Which one of your detectives caught all the dead girls?
探员? 他们已经去酒吧了
Detectives? They're at the bar already.
丢给你们了?
These yours?
他们定性为事故  把写报告的活儿扔给了我们
They chalked it up as an accidental and dumped the paperwork on us.
她发现了她们 所以得她写
She found them, she writes on it.
- 我是McNulty 市水警组的 - Beatrice Russell
- I'm McNulty, City Marine Unit. - Beatrice Russell.
你能确认身份了吗?
You got any IDs yet?
没有签证或者护照
No visas or passports.
有几页纸 但是看不出名堂来
A few scraps of paper, but nothing to make sense of.
大多是些俄文
Russian alphabet on most of it.
你只是好奇?
You just curious?
- 是的 - 为什么?
- Yeah. - Why?
就在前天 我在桥边捞到一具无名尸
Day before yesterday I fished out a Jane Doe from near the bridge.
但是没有失踪人口的报案
There's no missing person report on file.
我们有14个铺盖和13具尸体
We got 14 bedrolls and 13 bodies.
我那是凶杀
Mine was a murder.
凶杀 你开玩笑吧?
A murder, you're kidding me?
我们拍了些照片 如果你想看的话
We got some photos, if you wanna take a look.
今早我给太平间打了电话
I called the morgue this morning...
他们唯一的发现是 那些牙齿不是在当地做的
the only thing they can say is the dental work isn't local.
他们觉得应该是在海外
Overseas, they think.
这是你发现的姑娘?
Is that your girl?
我想是的
Think so.
这上面更好看
Looks better here.
你前天在桥边发现她在水里?
You got her in the water, day before yesterday, out by the bridge?
九点整 在Fort Armistead码头
0900 hours, by the Fort Armistead dock.
为什么你发现的女孩是被淹死在水里
Why would you have a murdered girl in the water...
而剩下的人却在Patapsco码头的 集装箱里窒息而死
and the rest of them are suffocating in a can at Patapsco?
哪里出了岔子?
What went wrong?
顶上的通风管被压瘪了
Air pipe up top got crushed.
很可能是发生在调度货物的时候
Happened when cargo shifted around, most likely.
他们用货物在集装箱前部做伪装 在后面25英尺的地方有个暗室
They had cargo up front of the container with a false back after about 25 feet.
前面看似有很多纸箱
You had cartons stacked in front...
但有一条窄道能通向暗室掩体的小门
but a tight passage to a small door in the false wall...
只能从外开启
opens from the outside only.
整个旅途她们都在这里?
They're in here the whole trip?
很可能不是
Probably not.
等她们上了海 通常船员里
Once they're at sea, there's usually someone in the crew...
会有个负责照看的人 "牧羊人"
who's in on it, you know, a shepherd.
他会放她们出来吃饭 活动 上厕所之类的
He let's them out to eat, move around, use the bathroom, whatever.
她们当时抓着墙壁 渴望空气
They were clawing at the wall for air.
法医应该也说了
That's what the medical examiner said anyway.
通风管道在哪儿?
Where's the air pipe?
那里有个洞 管道在上面
That's the hole. Pipe's up top.
你们这有很多偷渡的?
You get a lot of stowaways?
有一些吧 通常是海关和移民局发现他们
Some. Usually it's Customs or INS that finds them.
多数是些多米尼加人 海地人 或是那个地方的其他人
Most are Dominicans or Haitians, or from that part of the world, anyway.
从欧洲来的不多?
Not so much from Europe?
其实 911之后就变多了
A bit more since 9l1 1, actually.
我想是因为大家 不能像以前那样轻易搞到签证了吧
I think because people can't get in on visas anymore Iike they used to.
到了
There you go.
通常 如果看管的人能尽职
Usually, if the shepherd is doing his job...
他会尽量把这种集装箱放在货堆的最下面
he tries to put a can like this on bottom of the stack...
那他们就能打开箱门 放女孩们出来
so they can pop it and the girls just walk out on the floor of the hold.
那它的位置呢?
Where was this one?
- 瞧 - 什么?
- Look. - What?
你没觉得不对?
That look right to you?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
- 你说你是水警? - 是啊
- You said you were with the Marine Unit? - Yeah.
水警组和一群死在集装箱里的姑娘 有什么瓜葛?
What does the Marine Unit have to do with a bunch of dead girls in a can?
完全没关系
Not a thing.
你希望我做什么?
What do you want me to do?
你可以去找Lew神父
You can go to Father Lew,
让他把Sobotka的钱还回去
ask him to give Sobotka back his money.
也许 再换扇窗户
Switch the windows, maybe.
Stanis 你这辈子有看过哪个神父 把钱吐出来的?
You ever in your life seen a priest give money back?
那家伙为窗户掏了钱 那就是他的
The guy pays for a window, he gets a window.
我以为你们有交情
I thought you had suction.
市政厅的 我是有 Annapolis市(马里兰州首府)我也有
At City Hall, I got suction. Down Annapolis, I got suction.
但是除了罗马教皇 谁还和红衣主教有一腿? 算了吧
But who but the Pope has any drag with the cardinal? Get over it.
不过 他是怎么弄到那么多钱的?
How the fuck's he get that kind of money anyway?
这个问得好
Now, that's a good question.
我是说 整个码头工人兄弟会 在这镇上也没有1500人
I mean, the whole l.B.S. can't have 1,500 guys left in this town...
连100个检验员都没有
and there ain't 100 checkers.
他们还是有货船进来的...
They got the car ships coming in...
调度货物还是能让他们维持生计吧
the roll-onlroll-off cargo is keeping them afloat.
- 就靠这些? - 差不多
- That's all they got? - Pretty much.
过去六个月里码头兄弟会 雇了Bruce Dibiago的人
Past six months, l.B.S. hired Bruce Dibiago's people...
到Annapolis为他们游说
to lobby for them down in Annapolis.
他们在政治献金上很大方
They've been good with the political contributions.
出手阔绰
They're throwing around a lot of cash.
- 他们怎么做到的? - 你告诉我啊
- How can they? - You tell me.
Dibiago可不是省油的灯
Dibiago does not come cheap.
我们说的可是真金白银
This is real money we're talking.
你知道我在想什么吗
You know what I think?
我觉得Francis Sobotka"不干净"
I think Francis Sobotka's into some dirt.
你是警察 我不是
You're the cop, not me.
Grainery大楼?
The Grainery?
我听说Burrell会是下一任的局长
So I hear Burrell's gonna be the next police commissioner.
嗯 我见过更糟的呢
Yeah, I've seen worse.
瞧 如果是被另一个集装箱压瘪的
See, if it's crushed by another container,
那应该不止一个移动痕迹
it should've been one single movement...
也许会有两个 如果是来回
maybe two if something shifts, and then shifts back again.
而这个像是有人朝它砸了好几下
This looks like someone has been pounding on it in a bunch of spots.
瞧
See?
在认定之前 我需要找冶金专家求证一下
Before I rule it, I wanna go down with a metallurgist to be sure.
但的确 从外观上看...
But yeah, from the look of it...
你给自己找了13件凶案
you just bought yourself 13 homicides.
恭喜
Congratulations.
如果局长去了华盛顿 那就轮到你了 对吧?
If the commissioner goes down to Washington, it's you, right?
那得由市长决定 还要获得议会的支持
That's for the mayor to decide. I'd have to clear the council, too.
如果市长想要你 那就不会有什么问题
If the mayor wants you, that's not much of a problem.
要是和我一样在位那么久 那给自己树敌是难免的
You been around as long as me, you make a few enemies.
什么 那些一区的人?
What, the First District guys?
他们搞不起什么风浪
They're not gonna start nothing.
他们在力推Shipley
They're pushing Shipley.
瞧 这就是种族歧视
See, that's racist.
瞧 要是有谁不选你 而去选什么警监
You know, it personally offends me that anybody would reach down past you...
就因为他是个白人 我个人是绝对是看不过去的
to elevate some colonel just because he happens to be white.
你知道我会怎么做吗?
You know what I'm gonna do?
我会给市政厅的朋友打个电话
I'm gonna get on the phone and call my friends at the Hall.
让一区的人服服帖帖
That'll bring the First District in line.
那真是太好了
That's very kind.
那我有什么能为您效劳吗 Valchek警长?
And what if anything is there that I can do for you, Maj. Valchek?
看你说得多见外
Funny you should ask.
我需要一个专案组
I need a detail.
要由刑侦部挑大梁 不过我还是可以从我的区里抽些人手
CID people mostly, though I can spare some bodies out of my district, too.
查什么?
What for?
我那东南片里有些人出手很阔绰
I got some guys in the Southeast that are showing a lot of money.
- 港口的人 码头工人 -  码头工人兄弟会?
- Port guys, longshoremen. - I.B.S.?
我不是说要查整个工会
I'm not talking about going after the whole union.
只是当地一些看上去暴富的家伙
Just a couple of guys in one local that look fat.
也许是贩毒 或是平常的偷鸡摸狗
Drugs, maybe, or the usual thieving.
Frank Sobotka 你听说过这名字吗?
Frank Sobotka, you heard the name?
没有
No.
我觉得问题跑不出这个人
And I'm not saying the problem even goes past him.
你觉得他怎么了 Stan
What's he to you?
我觉得?
To me?
他是个混球
He's an asshole.
六个人 六个星期
Six men for six weeks.
由Rawls选人
Rawls will pick them.
你吃下肚的没有点的多
You ordered more than you ate.
这里外面挺冷的
It's cold out here.
Cedric
Cedric,
我不该又提出来 对不起
I shouldn't have brought it up again, I'm sorry.
你是对的
You're right.
你总是对的
You're always right.
我只是说你得现实点
I'm just saying you have to be realistic.
你过去做的事 让你落到今天这下场
You did what you did, and now you are where you are.
贬进了地下室
In the basement.
要是他们再下手狠点 你就直接"入土"了
If they buried you any deeper, you'd be under the damn building.
Burrell不会永远坐那个位置
Burrell won't be there forever.
Burrell会成为下任局长 你知道的
Burrell is going to be the next police commissioner, and you know it.
但是你有法律学位
But you've got the law degree.
加上你的警界资历 一半的事务所会视你如宝
With your police experience, half a dozen firms would think you're a prize.
你多的是选择
You've got options.
- 就因为他们... - 你说得没错
- Just because they don't-- - You're right.
你说得没错
You're right.
我会去交辞呈
I'll put in my papers.
谁要早饭?
Who wants breakfast?
天啊 正是时候
Christ, it's about time.
Lucky小店关着门 我不得不去了地铁那儿
Lucky's was closed. I had to go to the metro.
我还以为Mutt今天到北边去了
I thought Mutt be working North Point today.
他喜欢那些滚装船
He like them Ro-ro ships.
不 他老婆像是要动什么刀
No, his wife is having some kind of operation,
所以他换班了
so he gave back his hours.
那谁接手?
Who got them?
New Charles会顶Mutt的班
New Charles works for Mutt.
嘿 Zig 你今天开工吗?
Yo, Zig. You working today?
不 我是过来和你们这些老流氓 一起吃个早饭
No, came down here to have breakfast with you duper-faced fucks.
一天里它妈最重要的一顿 不是吗?
Most important goddamn meal of the goddamn day, right?
给他满上 Dolores Zig渴了
Set them up, Dolores, Zig is thirsty.
没错 我渴了
That's right, I'm thirsty.
你知道吗
You know what?
一口闷了 你们这群臭婊子
Bottoms up, you ugly whores.
- Nick - 什么事?
- Nick. - What's up?
过来
Come here.
我有个发财的机会
I got a line on something.
哦 是吗?
Oh, yeah?
你知道Curtis湾的White Mike吗?
You know White Mike from down Curtis Bay?
他打算让我分销一包货
He's gonna stake me to a package.
一包货?
A package?
白粉 Nicky 白粉
Dope, Nicky, dope.
我今天有活要干 Zig
I got work today, Zig.
是啊 而我不干活就有滚滚财源
Yeah, and I'm gonna make as much money not working.
你懂我说的吗?
You see what I'm saying?
那你它妈的找我干嘛?
So why the fuck you coming to me?
我想让你也入伙
I want you to come in on it with me.
你先出钱垫一垫 也许我的人会多分一点货儿给我们
You bring a little cash as money down, my man might give us a bigger package.
只要一转手 我们就有得赚了
We turn it around, we both get paid.
好了 船来了 先生们
All right, ship's in, gentlemen.
- 去它的买卖 Zig - 开工咯!
- Fuck that shit, Zig. - Time to work!
- Nicky 拜托 伙计 - 我能搭你的车吗?
- Nicky, come on, man. - Can I ride with you?
你愿意考虑一下吗?
Will you think about it?
Dolores 我能再来一杯吗?
Dolores, can I get another shot?
什么事?
What's up?
酒驾检查
DWI checkpoint.
请下车做一下酒精检测
Step out of the car for a Breathalyzer.
这才早上八点
It's 8:00 in the goddamn morning.
谁它妈的会在早上八点就喝醉?
Who the fuck gets drunk at 8:00 in the morning?
Bill 我不是想争论 技术上说那不是我们的管辖范围
Bill, I'm not arguing that the jurisdiction's not technically ours.
Patapsco河道绝对属于港务局
Patapsco's definitely Port Authority property
港口警察局负有管辖权
and the Port Police have the jurisdiction.
- 这个没什么好争论的 - 好
- That's not in dispute here. - Good.
但是他们没有调查凶案的能力
But they're not equipped for a death investigation.
你把13具尸体扔给他们 就等于扔给了我们
You dump 13 bodies on them, you're dumping them on us.
马里兰州警局势必要捡起这个烂摊子 我们已经焦头烂额了
MSP is gonna have to pick up that slack, overburdened as we are.
Robbie
我拼死拼活努力了四个月...
I have fought and scratched and clawed for four months...
把我的破案率提到了50%以上
to get my clearance rate up above 50%...
此时此刻 正好是51.6%
and right now, it stands at exactly 51.6%.
你知道要是我从你手上接下这13件无头案
Do you happen to know what my clearance rate will be...
我的破案率会有多难看吗?
if I take 13 whodunits off your hands?
39.4%
39.4%.
Bill 正如我说过的...
Bill, like I told you--
我们不是靠充傻冒才当上警监的 对吧?
We did not get to be colonels by being complete fucking idiots, right?
Robbie 你这个可怜蛋儿 看来你需要杯咖啡
Robbie, you poor bastard, you look like you need a cup of coffee.
这男人是神
The man is a god.
嘿 老大
Big chief.
我得在6点之前 把他带回最高戒备区 好吗
I gotta get him back to maximum security by 6:00, all right?
行 进来吧 伙计
Yeah. Come on in, man.
来 做这儿
Here, sit down.
吃点什么吧
Fix yourself something to eat, man.
- 不 伙计 我不饿 我吃过了 - 什么?
- No, man, I ain't hungry, I ate. - What?
你傻了吧 这玩意儿不赖
You crazy, this is good shit, man.
- 还是来几口吧 - 不了
- Better get in this. - No.
瞧 伙计...
Look, man...
如果他毁了你的屋子
if he tearing your room down, man...
我们就弄更多的东西进去
we keep bringing more stuff in.
让他拆不胜拆 你懂我的意思吗
It's gonna get so he can't tear it down fast enough. You feel me?
可他砸了我的小鱼 我没法...
He fucked with my fish though, I don't....
他没有必要那么做
He ain't have to go there, man.
这畜牲什么来头
What's up with this motherfucker?
你还记得Ladontay吗
You remember Ladontay?
住在Poe Homes的一个混混
Burner from over the Poe Homes?
放学之后在Carver停车场做了他
Caught him over at Carver parking lot after school?
我们干过?
We did that?
Tilghman是Ladontay表兄弟之类的
Tilghman was Ladontay's cousin or some such.
他见我认了罪 就来收拾我了
He found out I ate the charge, he busting my chops.
Ladontay?
我记都不记得了
I can't even remember that one.
你需要个计分牌来记录这些"血债"
You need a scorecard to keep up with your lethal ass.
Avon 他不肯放过我
Avon, he fixing to stay in my shit.
听着
Listen.
我会找他谈谈 好吗
I'm gonna talk to him, all right?
我会打点好的 好吗
I'm gonna set it straight. All right?
再说一遍他叫什么
What's his name again?
Tilghman 他在J区做日班
Tilghman, he work the dayshift on J-tier.
我会去见见他
I seen him around.
伙计 这些看守都是摆摆样子
Man, all these CO's are fronting and shit.
你能让保安给你带吃的进来
You got the guards bringing your meals in.
这个混蛋Tilghman表面上刚正不阿
This punk motherfucker Tilghman running around acting righteous...
暗地里把白货带进来干副业
but he bringing shit in here, steady slinging on the side.
别哭丧个脸 好吗
Don't fret. All right?
没事的
It's nothing.
我会搞定这件事
I'm gonna take care of it.
市局不接手?
The city won't take it?
没 它是港务局的地盘 所以归联邦州政府管辖
No, it's Port Authority property. It's state jurisdiction.
那就是Pikesville的马里兰警局
So it's MSP out of Pikesville.
案子需要真正查凶案的警察
Case needs real murder police.
你才不在乎 你只想整一整Rawls 对吗?
You don't give a shit. Just wanna fuck Rawls, don't you?
一点没错
Absolutely.
你能给我什么?
What can you give me?
这是为了报复你的上司?
This is about fucking over your boss?
如果他们不接手 那就轮到你了
If they don't eat the cases, then you will.
你需要什么?
What do you need?
首先 这个暗室有多大?
First of all, how big was the false compartment?
13乘7乘7(英尺)
13 by 7 by 7.
好吧 我们有13个成年女性 从正常到加速呼吸
Okay, we got 13 adult females, breathing at a normal to elevated rate...
那就是每分钟0.25升氧气
that's 0.25 liters of oxygen per minute...
每位受害人
per victim.
他是医生?
He's a doctor?
矿产局的
A State Bureau of Mines.
- 心理? - 矿产
- Minds? - Mines.
Tilghman警官
Officer Tilghman,
Tilghman警官 我俩能一起走走吗?
Officer Tilghman, could I parlay with you for a moment?
- 你是Barksdale 对吧? - 是的
- Barksdale, right? - Yeah.
- 瞧 我想知道你能否帮我个忙... - 不
- Listen, I want to know if you can help me-- - No.
抱歉?
Pardon me?
我说 不 狗娘养的
I said, no, motherfucker.
下楼去
Off the steps.
你现在又搞什么鬼?
What the fuck are you up to now?
你肯定想狠狠得整谁 我看得出来
You're deep into somebody's shit, McNulty. I can tell.
纯粹扯蛋
This is bullshit.
这些计算都已验算过...
Those computations were checked...
也被验尸官办公室确认
and confirmed by the medical examiner's office.
他们能断定死亡过程是三个小时内
They're accurate for time of death to within a three-hour window.
好吧 既然你这么说
Yeah, so you say.
你在水警组的手下实地勘测了集装箱
Your man in the Marine Unit did the measurements on the container.
我恰巧很了解这个在水警组的手下
I happen to know my man in the Marine Unit intimately...
他 无容置疑 是美国司法部门里
and he's, without a doubt, the most swollen asshole...
最无耻的混蛋
in American law enforcement.
我不会接下这13件凶案 不 先生
I am not eating 13 murders. No, sir.
要是她们在集装箱到岸之前就死了...
If they were already dead when the container hit the dock...
那么她们就是在船上被谋杀的
then they were murdered on board ship.
那就意味着Baltimore郡...
That means Baltimore County...
或者桥另一边的Anne Arundel郡
or Anne Arundel on the other side of the bridge...
要是死时还在深海湾
and if they're further down the bay,
那你们可以再找海岸警卫队一起扛
then you fellows with the Coast Guard can take it.
这不是市局的问题
This is not a city problem.
你们自己谈吧 伙计们
Talk amongst yourselves.
今晚你们中有一位将把案子带回去
One of you is taking this case home tonight.
不 Bill
No, Bill.
Atlantic Light号在夜里23点整 通过了Key大桥
The Atlantic Light passed the Key Bridge at 2300 hours...
离Patapsco河道2千码 抛锚
and laid up at anchor, 2,000 yards off Patapsco...
直到六点整 它才靠岸
until 0600 hours, when it docked.
而在地图上 那片区域属于Baltimore市
By the map, that's Baltimore city.
于是这艘船就在你的辖区内...
And that put the ship in your jurisdiction...
就在她们死亡的三小时内
for the three-hour window for the time of death.
Bill 你看上去需要好好喝一杯咖啡
Bill, you look like you could use a good cup of coffee.
Mikey
Mikey.
- 你好吗 - 不行
- What's up? - No.
什么不行?
No, what?
它妈的没门 你这贼眉鼠眼的家伙
No way, you little rat-faced piece of shit.
之前我给你的两包货都搞砸了
You fucked up the last two packages I gave you.
Mikey 瞧 伙计 那不是我
Mikey, look man, that wasn't me.
你要是有钱 Zig 你可以买个一丁点
You got money, Zig, you can buy a little weight.
你没有钱 哪儿凉快哪儿去吧
You got no money, go fuck yourself.
Mike 我以为我们是朋友
Mike, I thought we was friends.
你没搞丢上两包货?
Did you fuck up the last two packages?
- 算是吧 - 有把你揍惨吗?
- Sort of. - Are you beat to shit?
- 没有 - 滚吧 朋友
- No. - Take a walk, my friend.
- 你好吗 哥们 - 你好吗 公子哥
- What's up, man? - What's up, playboy?
Atlanta那边 暂时搞定了
That thing in Atlanta, settled for now.
我们有货了 你瞧
So we got that, you know.
好 我打你电话不是为了这事儿
Good. I ain't call you down for that, man.
把你叫到这来 是因为我们和这里的一个看守有点过节
Called you down here 'cause we got a CO in here with some bullshit.
- 谁? - 名字叫Tilghman
- Who? - Name is Tilghman.
他是Wee-Bey以前在学校停车场里 打死的一个家伙的亲戚
He kin to that boy that Wee-Bey dusted down over in that school lot.
他一直耿耿于怀
He can't let go of that shit, neither.
Tilghman? 好
Tilghman? Right.
听着 Brianna提醒了我
Listen, Brianna reminded me, man.
我们得履行承诺
We got promises we got to keep.
我知道 我听说了
I know, I heard.
你得去找找Dee的姑娘
You need to get with Dee's girl.
让她按时把小孩带到这里来
Have her bring that young one down here regular.
她得站出来 做她该做的
She need to step up and do her fucking part.
好
All right.
Dee情绪怎么样?
How's Dee taking it?
我是说 他该承担的还是得承担
I mean, he gonna do what need to be done, man.
你懂我的意思吗 Dee时不时地需要一点帮助
You know what I'm saying? Dee need a little help every now and again.
现在他没有脱离你 是吧?
You're not out of reach or nothing like that, right?
没 还没那样
No, nothing like that.
你确定?
You sure?
他为我们抗了不少
He's carrying a lot of weight for us, man.
Stringer 他是一家人 伙计
Stringer, he's family, man.
好吧 他是一家人
All right? He's family.
继续啊 Jimmy
Come on, Jimmy.
一口干了 宝贝
Take it to the head, baby.
来啊 告诉她你随时就绪
Come on. Tell her you were first in line.
这就对了
That's it.
There it is.
- 还有一杯 宝贝 继续 - 继续
- One more, baby, come on. - There you go.
- 够了 - 没呢 没呢 没呢
- That's enough. - No.
你得喝下全部14杯 坏小子
You gotta do all 14 of them bad boys...
每一杯都代表着你给Cole送去的 她们至亲的敬意
one for every member of the dear family you gave to Cole.
这杯敬Ray Cole 一位好警察 一个好男人
Here's to Ray Cole, a fine detective, and a goodly man.
Jimmy 看Jay Landsman的那张脸 他快要哭了
Jimmy, the look on Jay Landsman's face. He nearly fucking cried.
还有Rawls!
And Rawls!
Rawls 我发誓  他把自己关在办公室里一整天
Rawls, I swear to God, the man stayed in his office all day.
整个下午 他就把自己关在里面
All afternoon. He just stayed there with the door closed.
小心 你说得我快勃起了
Careful, you're giving me an erection.
继续啊
Come on now.
狗娘养的 这回你可是完胜
Motherfucker, you have outdone yourself this time.
从今往后 你是没机会再回来了 你心里一定有数
You ain't never coming back from this, you know that.
Lester 他们还能拿我怎样?
Lester, what the fuck can they do to me they haven't done?
我它妈的现在只能开条破船
I'm riding the goddamn boat.
去它的 我才不在乎呢 这是13号无名氏
Fuck it, I don't give a shit. Here's to Jane Doe 13.
好吧
All right.
管他们是不是要让我再多呆个11个年头
Eleven more years of whatever bullshit they throw at me.
我就打个报告 拿着抚恤金走人
I'm gonna put in my papers, take the pension and walk.
11年可是不短啊
Eleven's a long time to be on the shelf.
你来跟我说说 13年先生
Tell me about it, Mr. 13 years.
零四个月
And four months.
去它的
Fuck it.
他们吃了你 总得再吐出来
Chew you up, they gotta spit you back out.
第14杯
Fourteen.
他做到了
He did it.
操
Fuck.
悠着点 臭小子 我才不会扶你呢
Easy, motherfucker, I ain't picking up that shit.
走那边 走那边
Go that way.
- 伙计 还有谁在里头? - 他们扣下了La-la
- Man, anybody still in there? - They're keeping La-la.
他身上有旧案
He had an old warrant on him.
- 什么案? - 不知道 啥交通罚单之类的吧
- For what? - I don't know. Some traffic shit, man.
保释人在里头 想法子搞清楚呢
The bondsman's inside, trying to get it all figured out.
老兄 这它妈到底是犯什么邪?
Man, what the fuck was this all about anyway?
在我们上班的路上堵我们
Jerking us around on the way to work.
是我跟那个警察局的头头有点过节
It's a beef I got with a police boss.
Charlie Valchek的狗崽子弟弟
Charlie Valchek's little pissant brother.
你得搞定这事 伙计
You gotta get that taken care of, man.
- 我是说 这可有点失控了 - 我会搞定的
- I mean, this shit is out of hand. - I'm gonna take care of it.
嘿 要送你们一程吗?
Yeah, y'all need a lift?
- 回见 - 好 以后聊
- I'll see you. - All right, talk to you.
那个侏儒想开战 那就应战吧
That runt wants a war, he's got one.
反正也不该说
Not supposed to be talking anyway.
Bunk...Lester
Bunk, Lester.
嗯
Yeah.
你们两个胜出 无名尸是你们的了
You two winners are on the Jane Does.
什么 我们还没轮到呢 Jay
What? We're not up, Jay.
上个星期我们刚刚接了Pimlico的双重谋杀
We caught that double in Pimlico last week.
由Cole来接双重谋杀案
Cole's gonna take the double.
- 你们俩查集装箱里的女人 - Jay 这可不对
- You two got pussy in a can. - Jay, that ain't right.
你知道什么才不对吗?
You know what ain't right?
我们小队今年的破案率是负数
Our squad has a negative clearance rate for the year.
负数
A negative rate.
我不是说Ray Cole不是个好探员
Now, I'm not saying Ray Cole isn't a good detective.
但是我得把这14件案子"变黑"(黑色表示已破案)
But I need those 14 cases to go black...
所以我要派上最好的手下
so I got my best people on it.
Ray
Ray.
交给他们
Lay it on them.
发现现场的港口警察的名字和电话
Name and number of the port cop who processed the scene.
祝你们未来的辛苦能有回报 警探们
And the best of luck to you in all your future endeavors, Detectives.
狗娘养的
Motherfucker.
Beatrice Russell
Beatrice Russell.
她起码够养眼吧?
She pretty at least?
昨晚 你醉得操不动
Last night, you're too drunk to fuck.
今天 你又完全宿醉中
Today, you're too hung over.
什么东西对女人最没用?
What's the most useless thing on a woman?
- 什么? - 一个喝醉的爱尔兰男人
- What? - A drunken lrishman.
其实你不是真正的爱尔兰人 对吧?
But you're not really lrish, are you?
我连喝了14杯Jameson(爱尔兰威士忌)够格了吧?
I had 14 shots of Jameson. How's that for green?
你是够格了 好吧
You're green, all right.
你也是个笨蛋 谁会连喝14杯
You're also an idiot. Who does 14 shots?
你真是个孩子 McNulty
You're a child, McNulty.
以后凌晨两点 再不请自来
Show up at my door at 2:00 a.m. again without invitation...
我就报警了
I will call the cops.
你怎么会那么做?
Why would you wanna do that?
Jimmy
Jimmy.
我是你的女朋友吗 不是 你的老婆? 不是 你的知己?不是
Am I your girlfriend? No. Your wife? No. Your soul mate? No.
我它妈的到底算什么 Jimmy?
What the fuck am l, Jimmy?
我们在一起挺合得来
We're good together.
回答问题
Answer the question.
我一直对你很坦诚
I've been pretty honest with you.
我老婆想破镜重圆 我也这么打算 好吧
My wife wants to put it back together again, I'm gonna go for it, right?
你瞧 一起带孩子们...
You know, what with the kids and all....
你有阿司匹林吗?
You got any aspirin?
看在上帝的份上 Ronnie 我要死了
For Christ's sake, Ronnie, I'm dying in here.
一间真正的警察局会有电梯
A real police department would have an elevator.
你就是Russell?
So you Russell?
Bunk Moreland
Bunk Moreland.
Lester Freamon
Lester Freamon.
我还在等海岸警卫队  Delaware河分队的回音
I'm still on hold with the Coast Guard, Delaware River Detachment.
我们知道什么?
What do we know?
Atlantic Light正停靠在费城 今晚会开往Elizabeth港口
Atlantic Light is in Philly, heading for Port of Elizabeth tonight.
我正想请求他们 帮忙拦截
I'm trying to get them to hold her.
你们刑侦组有谁在负责此案吗?
Anyone from your CID working this?
没有 我听说大家对管辖权很有争议
Nope. I heard there's a big argument over jurisdiction...
你们警监得罪了所有人
and your colonel made everybody mad.
你们只有我可以找了
All you get is me.
还在等待中?
Still on hold?
我们可以上路再打
We can call this in from the road.
你们是市局凶杀科的?
You're with City Homicide?
- 那你一定知道Jimmy McNulty吧 - 是的 我们当他已经死了
- You must know Jimmy McNulty. - Yeah, he's dead to us.
先生们 请随意
Gentlemen, make yourselves at home.
我见过更糟的
I've seen worse.
这是公路管理局出租的 但是我们可以用它做驻外办事处
It's leased by the Highway Authority, but we can use it for an off-site.
- 暖气炉能用吗? - 能
- Furnace work? - It does.
还有电话线
And the phone lines.
要是你们得在这儿呆到夏天 那就需要按个窗机空调
You'll need window units if you're here come summer...
但是我觉得...
but somehow I got a feeling...
各位能齐心协力 在那之前结案
that you gents will put together a case quicker than that.
现在 这位...
Now, this here...
是我辖区的调查员 Roland Pryzbylewski
is my district investigator, Roland Pryzbylewski.
小子有天分
Kid's a prodigy.
你们有任何需要 都可以找他
Anything you need from me, you go to him.
先生们
Gentlemen,
目标人物是Frank Sobotka...
the target is Frank Sobotka...
以及所有和Frank Sobotka狼狈为奸的人
and anyone Frank Sobotka does his dirt with.
Roland会告诉你们细节 祝马到成功
Roland will fill you in on the details. Good hunting.
那谁签加班单
So who signs the overtime slips?
狗娘养的 你还真是个江洋大盗
Son of a bitch. You are a fucking thief, aren't you?
- 这就是我们的税钱换来的东西 - 我这手很漂亮 是吧
- This is where our taxes go. - I do good work, don't l?
让我们现在就把它送进箱子里去
Let's get it on the fucking can now.
Horseface 你这婊子养的
Horseface, you son of a bitch.
天 我剩下的那颗蛋蛋都要崩了
Christ, I'm gonna bust the only nut I got left.
加油 伙计们 还没我们平常的托盘重呢(承重一般为一吨)
Ain't no heavier than the pallets we usually handle.
最后的点睛之笔 小子们
Finishing touch, boys.
"国际码头工人兄弟会"一个经久不衰的联盟
一路平安啊
Bon voyage.
她上路了
There she goes.
抱歉 这里是管制区
This area's restricted.
海岸警卫队
好的 长官 没问题
Yes, sir, no problem.
- Amir 我们怎么还没开船? -  他们把船拦下了
- Amir, why don't we sail? - They're holding the ship.
- 谁? - 海岸警卫队 美国人
- Who? - Coast Guard, the Americans.
为什么?
Why?
操 Sergei 你差点弄断我的手
Fuck, Sergei, you almost break my hand.
把他带上车!
Bring him up!
- 祝你过得愉快 警官 - 好的 回见
- Have a good day, Officer. - Okay, I'll see you.
来享受一下吧
Now get up in there.
宵禁前最后的招待
Last call before lock-down.
利索一点
Make it snappy now.
喜欢吗?
How you like that?
不错 宝贝 很好
It's good, baby, it's beautiful.
不错 挺纯
Nice. Smooth.
多谢 伙计
Most def, man.
伙计 小心背后 多保重
Man, watch your back, be good, baby.
怎么样 哥们
What up, man?
嗯 他把那落下了
Yeah, he left that in here.
是他的
It's his.
那你还好吧?
So how you doing?
挺好
All right.
是吗?
Yeah?
我们需要谈一谈
Me and you gonna need to talk.
谁在船上?
So who's on board?
38个船员 14个也门人
Thirty-eight in the crew, 14 are Yemeni.
8个斯里兰卡人
Eight are Sri Lankan.
5个菲律宾人 剩下的都是游民
There are five Filipinos and the rest are from here, there, and back again.
- 有谁讲英文吗? - 你问他们的问题...
- Anybody speak English? - What you're asking them about...
如果有谁能回答上一句 我就惊艳了
I'll be amazed if any of them manages a word.
你的船长呢?
Where's your captain?
在海岸警卫队的办公室
At the Coast Guard office.
气死他了 因为明天我们 要停靠到新泽西的一个码头
Angry as hell because we're due on a New Jersey pier tomorrow morning.
你们到不了了
You ain't gonna make it.
我告诉你们 你们多扣我们一天 船舶代理就要多花费10万美元
I gotta tell you, every day that you hold us costs the shipping agent $100,000.
- Atlantic Light号是艘大家伙 - Atlantic Light号是个犯罪现场
-The Atlantic Light is a huge enterprise. -The Atlantic Light is a crime scene.
别想装硬汉
Don't try to play tough guy.
会受苦的不是我
I'm not the one getting my ass kicked.
回答我!
Talk to me!
告诉我 我该知道的
Tell me what I need to know.
让他起来
Get him up.
- 说说那些姑娘 - 没有姑娘 没有
-Talk about the girls. -No girls, nothing.
不会英文
No English.
你不会英文 却知道怎么跑?
You no speak English, but you know how to run?
你干嘛从船上逃走?
Why you run from ship?
那是它妈的什么意思?
What the fuck that suppose to mean?
他们在费城抓住了他
They got him in Philadelphia.
他发现海岸警卫队扣留船只时 跳船逃了
He jumped when he found out the Coast Guard was gonna hold the ship.
他哪儿的?
What is he?
Sergei说他像阿拉伯人
Sergei says he looks like an Arab.
他什么都不知道
He don't know nothing.
但是你还是不停地揍他
But you kept hitting him anyway.
去拿他的衣服
Get his clothes.
如果你不介意 我要抽一支
If you don't mind, I'm gonna have one.
来吧 我们聊聊
Come on, let's talk.
不会英文
No English.
告诉我 姑娘们出了什么事?
Tell me what happened to the girls?
不会说
No speak.
那会什么 你说什么语言?
What then? What do you speak?
得了 跟我说说 伙计
Come on, talk to me, friend.
原来是土耳其人?
Turkish?
你有个鹰钩鼻
You got that little hook on your nose.
别担心 爱国者
Don't worry, patrioti.
希腊与土耳其有很深的民族矛盾
我不反土耳其人 那是老皇历了 现在是新时代
I got nothing against the Turks. That's the old world. This is the new.
- Sam - Sam
- Sam. - Sam.
- 我什么都不知道... - 你知道的
- I don't know nothing about-- - You know.
你也会告诉我
And you're going to tell me about it, too.
之后...
After that...
就没你的事了 我保证
you're done, I give you my word.
我们打开集装箱 让她们洗漱
We popped the can to let them take a bath.
吸点新鲜空气
Get some fresh air.
你得明白 我的船员  他们已经很久没吃腥了
You gotta understand, my crew, they pulling on their pootsos for weeks.
这些姑娘 她们真的很漂亮
These girls, they looked pretty good.
- 你懂吗? - 嗯
- Katalavenis? - Yes.
他们手里有闲钱
The men had cash to spend.
我承认 我觉得有钱可图 但如此而已
I admit it, I saw chance for business, but that was all.
出了什么事?
What happened?
其中有个妓女不想卖了
One of the puttanas decided she didn't want to be a puttana no more.
有个男的就强上了她
This one guy got rough with her.
妓女死了
The whore died.
另一个看到了 我不知道该怎么做
The other ones saw. I didn't know what to do.
- 既然杀了一个 你就干脆杀光光 - 不 那是别人干的
- You kill one, then you kill them all. - No, that was another man.
另一个人 是谁?
Another man, what man?
有个女孩...
The one girl...
她们看见了 她们知道
they saw, they knew.
放松
Relax.
我向你保证过
I gave you my word.
- 当心你的鞋子 - 该死的土耳其佬
- Watch your shoes. - Goddamn Turko.
血流得像羊羔
Bleeds like a lamb.
一年里 每个妓女能带来25万的收入 那是多少?
In a year, each whore would bring a quarter million. What is it?
4百万
$4 million.
没了
Gone.
操(希腊语 谐音"马六甲")
Malaka.
算了 反正姑娘还会有
Anyway, there will be other girls.
这个...
This one...
别留下指纹
no fingerprints.
还有脸
No face.
没问题
That's not a problem.